export const chapter = "Chapter - 5: My Sweet Family";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What do we learn in our family?",
        optionA: "Advanced mathematics",
        optionB: "Basic things",
        optionC: "Nothing",
        correctAnswer: "Basic things",
      },
      {
        question: "Siya's family is described as:",
        optionA: "Small",
        optionB: "Big",
        optionC: "Joint",
        correctAnswer: "Small",
      },
      {
        question: "How many sisters does Garvit have in his family?",
        optionA: "None",
        optionB: "One",
        optionC: "Two",
        correctAnswer: "Two",
      },
      {
        question: "Nayra's family is an example of a:",
        optionA: "Small family",
        optionB: "Big family",
        optionC: "Joint family",
        correctAnswer: "Joint family",
      },
      {
        question: "In Nayra's family, who lives with her?",
        optionA: "Grandparents, parents, sister",
        optionB: "Parents and uncle-aunt",
        optionC: "Cousins and friends",
        correctAnswer: "Grandparents, parents, sister",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the common factor between all the families mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "They all have pets.",
        optionB: "They all have at least one child.",
        optionC: "They are families of different sizes.",
        correctAnswer: "They are families of different sizes.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who lives with Siya in her family?",
        optionA: "Grandparents",
        optionB: "Father, mother, and sister",
        optionC: "Only her father",
        correctAnswer: "Father, mother, and sister",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the size of Garvit's family?",
        optionA: "Small family",
        optionB: "Big family",
        optionC: "Joint family",
        correctAnswer: "Big family",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the composition of Nayra's family?",
        optionA: "Only her parents and sister",
        optionB: "Only her uncle and aunt",
        optionC: "Grandparents, parents, sister, uncle-aunt, and cousins",
        correctAnswer: "Grandparents, parents, sister, uncle-aunt, and cousins",
      },
      {
        question: "In which type of family does Garvit live?",
        optionA: "Small family",
        optionB: "Big family",
        optionC: "Joint family",
        correctAnswer: "Big family",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Siya lives with her ______, mother, and sister.",
        optionA: "father",
        optionB: "grandmother",
        optionC: "aunt",
        correctAnswer: "father",
      },
      {
        question: "Garvit lives with his parents and two ______.",
        optionA: "dogs",
        optionB: "cats",
        optionC: "sisters",
        correctAnswer: "sisters",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Nayra lives with her grandparents, parents, sister, uncle-aunt, and ______.",
        optionA: "neighbors",
        optionB: "friends",
        optionC: "cousins",
        correctAnswer: "cousins",
      },
      {
        question: "Hers is a ______ family.",
        optionA: "small",
        optionB: "large",
        optionC: "joint",
        correctAnswer: "joint",
      },
      {
        question: "In Nayra's family, who lives with her?",
        optionA: "Grandparents, parents, sister",
        optionB: "Parents and uncle-aunt",
        optionC: "Cousins and friends",
        correctAnswer: "Grandparents, parents, sister",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the size of Garvit's family?",
        optionA: "Small family",
        optionB: "Big family",
        optionC: "Joint family",
        correctAnswer: "Big family",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the common factor between all the families mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "They all have pets.",
        optionB: "They all have at least one child.",
        optionC: "They are families of different sizes.",
        correctAnswer: "They are families of different sizes.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who lives with Siya in her family?",
        optionA: "Grandparents",
        optionB: "Father, mother, and sister",
        optionC: "Only her father",
        correctAnswer: "Father, mother, and sister",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the composition of Nayra's family?",
        optionA: "Only her parents and sister",
        optionB: "Only her uncle and aunt",
        optionC: "Grandparents, parents, sister, uncle-aunt, and cousins",
        correctAnswer: "Grandparents, parents, sister, uncle-aunt, and cousins",
      },
      {
        question: "In which type of family does Garvit live?",
        optionA: "Small family",
        optionB: "Big family",
        optionC: "Joint family",
        correctAnswer: "Big family",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Siya lives with her father, mother, and sister.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Garvit's family is described as a small family.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Nayra's family is an example of a big family.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Garvit has two brothers in his family.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In Nayra's family, she lives with her grandparents, parents, sister, uncle-aunt, and cousins.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "All the families mentioned in the text have at least one child.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Siya's family consists of grandparents, parents, and her sister.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Nayra's family is described as a joint family.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Garvit's family is described as a small family.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In Siya's family, she lives with her father, mother, and her two brothers.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
